(brooding music)
(static hissing)
(people whispering)
(pensive music)
(brooding music)
(brooding music continues)
(utensils clinking)
(mellow music)
(pitcher thuds)
(plates thudding)
- Ah, sorry.
- (sighs) Ma'am, that's tea.
- (sighs) Shoot, um, I'll
go get you a new one, sorry.
- Ma'am, I asked
for this with no onions.
- Sorry, um, I'll have
them make you a new one.
Keep that plate. I'll
just get another plate.
(door clattering)
- I don't understand why
you can't just admit it.
Admit what?
I wasn't doing anything.
Don't be crazy.
- Don't gaslight
me. I'm not crazy.
I saw you ogling that cashier.
Every time she came around,
you were burning a hole
through her with your eyes.
You don't get it.
I, I just want
you to acknowledge it.
- I'm sorry. I really
don't wanna fight with you.
- I'm sorry is
not an acknowledgement
of what I'm asking you.
(envelopes rasping)
Hello? Are
you gonna say something?
- It's here.
- What is?
(phone ringing)
- It came, son of a bitch.
Ah, give it here.
(employees
chattering indistinctly)
- Yeah, hurry and open it, man,
'cause we really need this.
Then we need this score to
cover this short, man, fuck.
- Hey, Mo, can I get no onions
on that enchilada for two?
I'm sorry. I thought I'd
said that the first time.
- You did.
I just don't give a shit.
- Mo.
- I'm just
kidding, three minutes.
- [Tracy] (sighs) Thanks.
- How's your dad?
- Better, actually.
Yeah, he's, uh, standing
up on his own now.
Once he can take himself
to the bathroom on his own,
that's when we'll know he
actually wants to live.
Yeah, hopefully,
at this rate, though,
I'll be able to go back
to school next semester.
- Hooker?
- (scoffs) Chemical engineer.
- Oh, fancy hooker.
- Dick.
Hey, uh, is
there anything for me?
- I didn't look.
What'd your doc say
about your headaches?
- (sighs) Another concussion.
Anymore, and I will have
irreparable brain damage.
- I guess you better not be in
another drunk driver's path.
- I know, right?
It's here.
- The acceptance letter for
the night out, we're in.
- The contest?
- Cha-ching million bucks,
Europe, here we come.
- Do we have flashlights?
- Flashlights?
- Yeah, you always pack
a fucking flashlight
when you go to
haunted places like this.
- Yeah.
- You never know.
- This is gonna be epic!
(lips smacking)
(Mandy laughs)
(phone ringing)
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Yes.
- Fuck yeah.
(brooding rock music)
(brooding rock music continues)
(footsteps plodding)
♪ Just fade away ♪
- [Dusty]
Welcome to the Val Verde.
- [Robert] Thank you, is
this where we check in?
(bag thuds)
- Have a seat.
Someone will be
down to explain everything
to you once everybody arrives.
(mellow music continues)
(footsteps plodding)
- Uh, can I get a drink?
- In a minute.
♪ I surrender ♪
(glass clinking)
(liquid sloshing)
♪ To the current ♪
♪ Let the water pull me in ♪
♪ Oh, promise ♪
- Hello, Page.
Goodbye, Page.
- Kids these days, they
don't say much, do they?
How about that drink, man?
- I said in a minute. We
gotta wait for the boss.
(breath whooshing)
(footsteps plodding)
(water sloshing)
- Fucking right.
Yo, Vinny, baby, how you doing?
Ah, sorry, nope.
Did not mean to call ya that.
- [Parker] Uh,
this could be interesting.
- Yep, at the hotel
now, it's a done deal.
Yeah, no, no, no, please, yep,
please tell 'em
it's a, it's done.
Uh, uh, I'll have
the money tomorrow.
(dogs barking)
Hello.
Fuck you.
(footsteps plodding)
(water sloshing)
What's up? Steven.
- So?
- Oh, shit,
you're Devante Parker.
Dude, you had
a huge contract with Miami
and then killed that family.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, I didn't
kill anybody, all right?
- Dude, that's gotta suck, man.
You really (laughs) fucked
the dog on that one.
(laughs) Damn.
- You know what?
I'll be back in the league
in two years, right?
Suspension, so I'll still
be wealthy and successful.
You'll still be broke
and looking like that.
This is just a money grab
for me in the off season.
- All right.
- Yeah, remember that.
Tried to be humble.
- Sensitive.
- [Parker] Start that bullshit.
(footsteps plodding)
(bags thudding)
- What's up?
(Steven exhales)
(hat thuds)
(Parker exhales)
(Tracy scoffs)
(Tracy sighs)
(building creaking)
(item thudding)
(building continues creaking)
(stairs creaking)
(Charles sighs)
- Good afternoon,
contestants and guests.
I'm Charles, your host.
(Steven sighs)
- Cell phones, right now,
no exceptions, no P pads,
no weird watches, nothing.
(brooding music)
(footsteps plodding)
(brooding music continues)
(phones clanking)
(floor creaking)
(brooding music continues)
(fingers tapping)
(stairs creaking)
- [Charles] Page, honey,
have you had lunch?
- No, Dad.
- Well, let's lay
off some of that soda.
- I want a drink for lunch.
- How about water?
- Ice, it's made of water.
(brooding music)
- Yeah, I guess so.
Make yourself a sandwich.
Dusty, can I get a drink?
- Oh, I will take an
Arnold Palmer, please.
(item clanking)
(briefcase clattering)
- Is, uh,
that it? That's the money?
- Can I see it?
- This hotel's been
haunted since it was built.
The boiler exploded
and killed five workers
in a horrific fire.
And the ghost was sent streaming
through the pipes into
every room in this hotel.
Every few years,
someone else dies,
and for the last 100 years,
no outsider has been
able to spend the evening
on the anniversary
of that explosion.
The ghost forces 'em out.
The night of death's gonna end,
and none of
you are gonna be here.
You'll leave hysterical,
and some of
you will never be the same.
- Well, unless
some of us aren't bitches
and sleep like a baby.
- Bitches, huh?
- Oh, fucking relax. I
didn't mean that that way.
- Oh, sure, next you're gonna
start calling people pussies.
- Some of you, anyway.
(latches clicking)
- Well, if any of you're lucky
enough to be here at sunrise,
this is the prize.
(brooding music continues)
(lid thuds)
You'll be getting
keys to your rooms,
and I suggest you use 'em.
You stay there
'cause it's in the hallways
and the calm places, that's
where the problems have been.
If you leave the hotel,
your prize is forfeited.
- Okay, but what if none
of us leave the hotel?
What about that?
- That's never happened.
- Okay, but I understand that,
but what if that does happen?
- Then the prize would
be equally distributed
amongst the survivors.
- So what do
you get out of this?
(bottle rasping)
(liquid sloshing)
- We get to watch
you piss yourselves
(ominous music)
before you die.
(glass rasping)
(liquid sloshing)
(Steven laughs)
(glass clinking)
(liquid sloshing)
(glass rasping)
(ominous music)
Last chance.
- (sighs) Just
give me my room key, man.
(cork squeaking)
(keys jangling)
- We will all be
leaving after dinner.
We don't dare stick around
once everything
starts to get freaky.
- It's freaky.
(Mandy and Shelby laughing)
- So what do you guys think?
- What, like,
a bunch of spooky noises
and holograms are
gonna scare us off?
- Have you guys ever heard of
anyone actually doing this?
- Not that I heard of.
I found out about this
a year ago when it said,
10 years running, no one
could stay all night.
- Well, did anyone say
what scared everyone off?
- Not that I read.
- Well, what about the money?
How come it's not 100,000?
How come it's a million now?
- Well, it keeps
growing year after year.
Nobody's winning.
- And where did it come from?
- Trust fund or something,
um, maybe "Brewster's Millions."
- Oh, like
"Brewster's Millions"?
- [Robert] But people
end up in the hospital.
- You're not
gonna hear about a trust
or what forced anybody out
'cause everyone signs a
nondisclosure agreement, right?
Which means if
you tell what happens here,
you gotta pay a million dollars.
You got that, Steven?
(Steven laughs)
- So this guy's just
fine with six strangers
cruising his joint all night
with a million bucks upstairs?
- Okay, look, we only
have to be in our room
until the sun comes up.
Come on, lover. Let's go
lock the door and talk
about how we're
gonna spend our money.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, pump the brakes.
You guys are a fucking couple?
How the hell
did you both get in?
I had to wait three years
to get in on this deal.
- We just applied and got
approved like everyone else.
(lips smacking)
- That is gonna be fucking
hot, though. Am I right?
- You're fucking sick.
- Need that bottle.
- Cool.
(keys jangling)
(Robert sighs)
(brooding music)
(keys jangling)
(door clattering)
(brooding music continues)
(bag thuds)
(door thuds)
(brooding music continues)
(hand rasping)
(floor creaking)
(brooding music continues)
- If there are cameras in
here, they're hidden well.
(door squeaking)
(brooding music continues)
(floor creaking)
(door clattering)
(brooding music continues)
(floor creaking)
(hand knocking)
- Anyone in here?
(brooding music continues)
(latch clicking)
(switch clicks)
(brooding music continues)
(door squeaking)
(door thuds)
(brooding music continues)
(flowers rustling)
(curtains rasping)
(items clattering)
(painting thuds)
(brooding music continues)
(window rasping)
(cigar crackling)
(brooding music continues)
(window rasping)
(cigarette crackling)
(brooding music continues)
(latch clicking)
(footsteps plodding)
- Is that the toilet?
- Yeah.
- Did you check for cameras?
- (laughs) Um, yeah, but
I, I didn't find anything.
- How well did you check?
- (laughs) I,
I think pretty well.
I don't know. I would
just check for myself.
- Okay, I'll risk it.
- Good luck.
(footsteps plodding)
(brooding music)
(latch clicking)
(door squeaking)
(brooding music continues)
(finger taps)
- Is there space
between your finger
and your reflection
in a two-way mirror?
- [Shelby] Uh, space, I think.
- Are you sure?
- No, space means
it's a real mirror.
- Are you sure?
- I don't know. I'm sorry.
Uh, just cover yourself up. I'm
sure it's not the first time
some creep's watched you pee.
- Are you back there
watching me, you creep?
(hands thudding)
Do you like that? Are
you a dirty little freak?
(clothes rustling)
(brooding music continues)
(switch clicking)
(switch continues clicking)
(brooding music continues)
I hope you are
watching, you pig.
(clothes rustling)
(brooding music continues)
(urine pattering)
(toilet water sloshing)
Well, I hope you liked that.
I'm charging you a million
bucks for that show.
(dramatic music)
Oh, shit, you scared me.
- Who were you talking to?
- I was just messing with the
creep that might be watching.
- Pig.
- You're the one
sneaking around. (laughs)
- Well, maybe we should give
him a little show of our own.
- Who's being gross now?
- I might be. Are you saying
you're not interested?
- Oh, I'm always interested.
- Ooh.
Oh. (laughs)
(brooding music)
(door squeaking and clattering)
(cigar crackling)
(Parker sighs)
(remote clicks)
(crowd cheering)
(Parker laughs)
- What people do for money.
(crowd cheering)
7:00.
Mm.
(cork squeaking)
(liquid sloshing)
(pensive music)
(Steven sighs)
(glass thuds)
(Steven exhales)
- [Neighbor] Hey.
(hand knocking)
- Jesus.
Fuck.
(Steven sighs)
(brooding music)
Who is it?
Jesus Christ.
All right, listen. I
don't scare that easy.
So beat it.
(brooding music continues)
(hand knocking)
(door clattering)
(Steven speaking faintly)
(dramatic music)
Jesus.
(body thudding)
Ah, ah, uh, help!
(blood sloshing)
Help!
- What was that?
- It's starting.
(brooding music)
- What is?
- They're trying
to scare us, right?
- Well, let's cover the
noise with some screaming.
(both laughing)
(brooding music continues)
(lips smacking)
(both breathing heavily)
- Help!
(door clattering and squeaking)
- [Tracy] What
the hell did you do?
- Nothing,
I just opened the door
and, and just,
just found her like this.
- I heard you yelling.
What did you do to her?
- Nothing! Just
shut the fuck up, lady.
- [Tracy] Somebody help!
There's a girl
that's been killed.
(door clattering)
- Yo, what's going on?
- That girl, she's dead.
- (sighs) Hold on.
So, what, should
we call the police?
- With what phone?
(zipper whizzing)
(clothes rustling)
(both laughing)
(lips smacking)
- Oh, my.
(Shelby laughs)
- It's just a part of the game.
- No, I heard them
fighting. He killed her.
- [Steven] Oh,
my God, I did not.
I just opened the door to this.
(dramatic music)
- Oh, fuck.
Now what?
- More of the plan.
- Oh.
(item rustling)
(door clattering and squeaking)
- [Parker] I can't see shit.
- [Tracy] Somebody get a light
on before he kills us all.
- [Steven] Ah,
you're insane, woman.
Stop. Quit, quit your yapping.
- Come back to bed, lover.
Let the others worry
about the fucking game.
(bedding rustling)
(lips smacking)
(Mandy breathing heavily)
(switch clicks)
(dramatic music)
What the fuck is that?
- I didn't see anything.
- Babe, you didn't see?
- [Shelby] How did they get
in with the door locked?
- How did they get out
without unlocking the door?
(brooding music)
- Where the fuck did she go?
(footsteps plodding)
- [Parker] Open the door.
- You open the door, football.
- [Tracy] I'll open
the door, you cowards.
(latch clicking)
(brooding music)
- It stops right here.
There's no body.
- Fake fucking shit. (scoffs)
- Wait, do
you think this is staged?
- Do you think it's staged?
- Damn, bro,
they're doing too much.
Think I'm gonna call it quits.
(Tracy laughs)
I'm gonna get Charles.
- You're one to talk about
knowing when to call it quits.
(brooding music continues)
(dramatic music)
(door clattering)
(items thudding)
(zipper whizzing)
- Show me the money, baby.
(device beeping)
Hiding the gold
in the basement, eh?
(Robert laughs)
- Bro, your phone sounds
horrible right now, man,
like you're some kind of a
fucking robot or something.
- I can hear you.
Hey, just wanted to let you know
that the kids are where
your wife left them.
Just like you said, I'll
check on them in a bit.
- No way. (laughs)
(fist thuds)
I fucking knew it, man.
My wife has her shit together.
All right, let me know.
- I will.
There's a lot of
crazy shit going on here,
screaming like a bunch of
kids, lights turning off.
- Yeah, just be careful.
- Hey, yo, Charles.
(hand knocking)
(brooding music)
Charles.
(hand continues knocking)
(door squeaking)
Hey, man, where's Charles?
- There, there's
a dead body downstairs.
- Did you hear what she
said? What's going on, man?
Stop standing there looking
stupid, man. Do something.
- Gross.
- Oh, this part
of the game, right?
Hey, can
you get Charles, please?
Hey, Charles!
(door squeaking and slamming)
Weirdo.
- Let's just go see if
he's at the bar downstairs.
- All right.
(footsteps plodding)
(brooding music continues)
Yeah, see, that's why people
like Dusty get smacked.
Before the contract, I woulda
smacked the shit outta that...
- Where were you guys?
- Someone was
dead at Steven's door.
- What?
- Wait, wait, wait.
I'm not saying all that.
That girl Page, it
looked like she was dead.
She was laying
there for one minute.
Then she disappeared.
Steven thinks it's a hoax.
- Okay, but Steven was
fighting with her in the hall,
like, right before that, so
he could just be covering.
- Well, we just
saw someone in our room
when the light turned off.
- Wait, what? Just now?
- [Mandy] Yeah,
like, a few minutes ago.
- You see who it was?
- No, but we're
gonna go find Charles.
We were gonna go do that,
too. Just come with us.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, it's okay.
What you looking
at me like that for?
- I don't trust you.
- What's wrong with you?
(latch clicking)
(brooding music continues)
(gun thuds)
(case clattering)
(shoe rasping)
(shoe thuds)
(footsteps plodding)
(eerie music)
- The hell? The fuck is that?
- [Mandy] Uh, uh, I think
it's just a reflection
on the glass from that lamp.
- That's not a reflection.
There's a, a shadow being
cast in the hallway.
- No, someone is
definitely back there.
- Uh, Charles, is that you?
Charles?
(eerie music continues)
- Can't find any switches.
- Yeah, well,
it's, it's the breaker.
The switches are already on.
(eerie music continues)
(switches clicking)
- Yo.
- There.
- Was somebody else
doing what you just did?
- Yeah, they probably
just broke out
before our eyes adjusted,
sick motherfuckers
playing that game.
- Are you gonna go check it out?
- Oh, me, why, 'cause I'm a man?
No, I'm a feminist, too, so
right after you, young lady.
- I'll go, you chicken.
- I'll come with.
- I'll be here getting a drink.
Enjoy yourselves.
(brooding music)
(liquid sloshing)
(cork squeaks)
(bottle thuds)
(Parker exhales)
(door clattering)
(brooding music continues)
- (groans) What the fuck?
- Oh.
- [Man] Get up!
Damn.
- I'm sorry, please, no.
(item thudding)
(solemn music)
(switch clicks)
- Parker? Parker.
- Look.
- Oh, my God.
(dramatic music)
(Mandy screaming)
- Blood.
(feet pattering)
(brooding music)
- [Shelby] Here
you go. I'm gonna...
(Mandy speaking faintly)
- [Shelby] Okay.
- [Charles] I wouldn't
do that if I was you.
- [Mandy] What?
- You go outside.
You forfeit the game.
You lose.
- Okay, where's Parker?
- How would I know?
(Shelby sighs)
(footsteps plodding)
- [Shelby] You're
not going anywhere.
(shoes clacking)
(brooding music continues)
- Ladies, have a nice evening.
I'll see you in the morning.
- [Shelby] Where are you going?
You have to call the police.
(door clattering)
- Okay, that's it.
I'm waiting the rest
of this out in my room.
- Yeah, I think
we should, too. Come on.
(footsteps plodding)
(brooding music continues)
(door creaking)
(stairs creaking)
(door squeaking and clattering)
(footsteps plodding)
(brooding music continues)
(lighter clicks)
(dramatic music)
(brooding music resumes)
(crickets chirping)
(Parker gasping)
- Hey.
Hey!
(chair creaking)
Let me outta here!
(chair clattering)
Help!
Let me out! Fuck this game!
Let me outta here!
(brooding music)
(brooding music continues)
(Robert breathing heavily)
(floor creaking)
(Parker gasping)
Okay, okay, okay,
wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Okay, okay.
Okay, you got
it. You got it, okay.
(blade rasping)
(brooding music)
(feet pattering)
(feet rasping)
- Shit.
(door slamming)
(feet pattering)
(door squeaking)
Shit!
(hand knocking)
Dammit! Let me in.
I wasn't leaving,
you son of a bitch!
This is bullshit! Fuck you!
Let me in!
(siren wailing)
This is bullshit. Fuck you!
Let me in! Fuck you!
Let me in, you son of a bitch!
- [Officer]
Hey! What are you doing?
(door slamming)
- Trying to get in.
- We just got
a call that a homeless man
has been breaking down the
door, trying to get in.
Leave, or we'll arrest you.
- I'm staying here. This is
where I'm staying tonight.
- You're not
staying here anymore.
Move along. I'm
not gonna say it again.
- I was just in there,
like, 30 seconds ago.
When did you get that call?
- Wait, is
that blood on the ground?
- Shit, I'm leaving.
- Wait right there, Robert.
- How the fuck
do you know my name?
- I buy stocks from your office.
- [Robert] Buy
fucking shit from me!
I'm a corporate broker!
(Parker gasping)
(siren wailing)
(Parker screaming)
- Help! I'm down here!
Help me! (screams)
(Parker grunts)
(chair clattering)
(siren wailing)
(Parker grunting)
(chair clattering)
(Parker groaning)
- Do you really think
something could be happening?
- I doubt it, but I wanna
catch these idiots in the act.
I know that girl's
in on it, but Parker,
could he be an actor?
Do we care?
(Mandy laughs)
(latch clicking)
(both laughing)
(Parker screaming and groaning)
- Okay, okay, wait.
(brooding music)
Okay, I quit, I'll quit.
(Parker groaning)
(brooding music continues)
(footsteps plodding)
(pencil rasping)
(brooding music continues)
(pencil continues rasping)
- One drop per
fluid ounce of chlorine.
One drop per
(cap clanking)
(liquid sloshing)
Fuck it.
(Steven laughs)
(bottle thuds)
That ought to
clear the place out.
(lid rasping)
And then I cash in.
(container thuds)
(Steven laughs)
(container rasping)
Uh-huh.
(zipper whizzing)
(door creaking and clattering)
(Tracy exhales)
(floor creaking)
(footsteps plodding)
(lips smacking)
(Shelby breathing heavily)
(lips continue smacking)
(Shelby gasps)
(pensive music)
(item rasping)
(container clanking)
(feet pattering)
(door clattering)
- Okay, what do
want, you fucking pervert?
I knew it was you,
Robert, you fucking sicko!
When this is done, I
will crush your skull!
(door clattering)
(pensive music continues)
(door creaking)
(door clattering)
- Robert.
(floor creaking)
(pensive music continues)
Where are you, you tedious fuck?
(items clattering)
(pensive music continues)
(floor creaking)
(brooding music)
(item clanking)
(brooding music continues)
My fucking man.
(water sloshing)
(brooding music continues)
(bag rustling)
(finger tapping)
Meathead, you in there?
Meathead.
(fingers tapping)
(brooding music continues)
(container thuds)
(phone buzzing)
(feet pattering)
(brooding music continues)
(chair clattering)
(window squeaking)
(brooding music continues)
(chair creaking)
(lid rasping)
- Is this bleach?
Must be an ammonia vial.
Guess the bearing
breaks the vial,
mixes the bleach with the
ammonia, creating chlorine gas.
Why the fuck would you put
this in a plastic bottle?
I mean, it's not gonna
bust and explode. (laughs)
God, why are men so stupid?
(phone buzzing)
(latch clicking)
(phone continues buzzing)
(door clattering)
(brooding music)
(phone beeps)
- Hello?
(lid clanking)
(bearing clinking)
(brooding music continues)
(cork squeaking)
- There, now we have a
real chlorine gas grenade.
(lid clattering)
(lid squeaking)
- [Nathan] Who's this?
- This is Steven. Who's this?
(chair squeaking)
- [Nathan] Steven, how'd
you get this phone?
- Well,
we aren't allowed phones,
so how did Robert get
it past the front door?
- Where's Robert?
- Beats me.
I just found this
phone in the hallway
with a bunch of
other electronic shit.
- When did you see Robert last?
- I don't know, around the
time we found that dead girl.
- Girl died?
- Ah, probably not,
just some more bullshit
to try to scare us.
Hey, uh, you want to tell me
what all this
electronic gear is for,
or do I tell
Charles your little plan?
- Don't show Charles.
It's not gonna end well
for anybody, all right?
In 2016, he caught
someone with a cell phone.
He ended the whole thing,
replaced the entire guest list.
The guy with
the cell phone, he sued him
for half a million dollars
for breach of contract.
- Oh, I'm not losing my
chance at this money.
- No, Steven, it doesn't seem
as if that would
be helpful to you.
But you know what?
It does look like you're
gonna have to explain
to your firm you've how been
using their closing funds
to fund your gambling habit
and robbing Peter to pay Paul.
It's gonna get
crucified like Christ.
- And how do you know that?
- I know there's enough to see
that you're an ally,
not an opponent here.
Cutting you in for half
a million barely gets you
outta your mess, but it
does clear your bookie,
who, may I remind you, is
gonna kill you tomorrow.
- All right,
what do you want from me?
(fingers tapping)
(brooding music continues)
- Find Robert. Help
him complete his task.
We'll cut you in for 500K.
(Steven laughs)
- How much is there?
- For you, half a million
dollars or nothing.
- Okay, fine, but he's not
in his room. I just checked.
- Well, find him.
Leave the phone
in your room, though.
Have Robert call me when
he turns up, all right?
- Okay, fine,
but just wait, wait.
Has anyone ever
died in this hotel
over the years doing this?
- No, it's all gimmicks
and terrifying tricks,
lots of injuries, though,
which is why
you signed all those waivers.
He's liable for none of it.
Don't get hit in
the head with a brick.
- And why would you say that?
- Someone got hit in
the head with a brick.
They were in a coma
for a couple of years.
- Fuck.
(brooding music continues)
(phone beeps)
(antenna clanks)
(bag thuds)
(bag rustling)
(Steven exhales)
(hands patting)
(Steven laughs)
(latch clicking)
(door squeaking)
(feet pattering)
(brooding music)
(dramatic music)
(feet rasping)
- [Robert] Is
this fucking real blood?
Fuck!
(brooding music)
- Come on please. Let me go.
Let me go. Let me go.
(photo rasping)
Help. Robert, is that you?
Help!
- Parker, are you in there?
- [Parker]
Okay, uh, I'm in here.
- Oh, Parker, you're alive?
- I'm in here.
- Oh, man, dude, fuck, fuck.
- Yeah, get that.
Help me out, man. This
motherfucker's trying to
kill me.
- Oh, shit, man.
- Yeah.
- This does not look good.
- Get me-
- Does not look good.
Holy fuck,
let's get out of here.
- Cut this shit over here.
Come on, man.
- Get the fuck outta here!
(brooding music continues)
(feet pattering)
Your neck, man.
- Yeah, motherfucker
got me in there.
Is it deep?
- No, not at all.
There's fucking blood
everywhere. What the fuck?
- Shit, I don't know.
I thought he cut
me deep. You sure?
- No, it's not cut at all.
What the fuck is this?
- Check the cops.
(feet pattering)
(brooding music continues)
Somebody must have got 'em.
- They were just
here a little while ago.
- They're already dead.
- It has to be
part of the game, man.
- We're out the game.
We're outside.
- Fuck we are, man.
- There's camera's right there.
- [Robert] I don't give a fuck.
- They gotta get us,
right? They gotta catch us.
(feet pattering)
(crickets chirping)
(brooding music)
(Shelby speaking indistinctly)
(hand rasping)
(towel and clothes rustling)
(door clattering and squeaking)
- What the hell are you doing?
- What? Nothing.
You know what?
I just saw that Robert fuck
going door to door listening in.
- When?
- I don't know,
10 minutes ago maybe.
You guys seen him?
- Uh, no, we've been
in our room all night,
ever since we left you.
- Fuck off, I heard you
guys screaming in your rooms
like little kittens on fire.
- Yeah, because somebody
was outside our door.
- So you saw him?
- No, and
we didn't see you either.
Where are you going now?
- Lobby, gonna
go try to find him.
- Good luck,
we're not leaving our room
for the rest of the night.
- Fucking pussies.
- Fuck you.
Go be a hero. We're here to win.
And if I catch you outside
of my fucking door again,
I will smash you.
- That's
assault. That's assault.
You watch it.
(door clattering and squeaking)
- What?
No.
- Yes.
- No.
(feet pattering)
(brooding music)
(doorknob clattering)
Be quiet, girl.
You're so damn loud.
- Let him hear me. I
know he's full of shit.
(latch clicking)
(brooding music continues)
(bag rustling)
(Shelby sighs)
(zipper whizzing)
(brooding music continues)
- Nathan?
- No clue, call it.
- [Nathan] Robert?
- Robert?
- Who's this now?
- Why does Steven
have Robert's phone?
Why, why does
anyone have a phone?
- [Nathan] Who are you?
- Mandy.
- Mandy, is Shelby with you?
- How do you know who we are?
- [Nathan] I'm an investigator
with the US Marshal's Office.
Look, Robert's been engaged
to help us with a crime.
Steven found his phone.
He's been tasked
to help us find Robert.
We haven't heard from him
in a couple of hours, okay?
- Okay, well,
we're not looking for him,
but we'll let
you know if we find him.
- [Nathan] Look, I need you to
look for him. It's important.
- Okay, well, uh, we'll let
you know if we find him.
(phone beeps)
(door squeaking)
(door clattering)
(pensive music)
(door creaking)
(brooding music)
(latch clicking)
- There's no way
that wasn't an act.
- I mean, if he was
drunk, it makes sense.
- I don't know. Let's just...
(item thudding)
(brooding music continues)
(latch clicking)
- What the hell was that?
- Charles just went
upstairs with a sandwich.
- I knew they weren't
leaving, those lying fuckers.
- I mean,
the door closed, and then,
and then we heard the scream.
- 'Kay, well, did y'all hear,
like, voices or anything else?
- Nothing.
- Do you think we should go
upstairs and check it out?
- No, this is all, this is part
of the thing
they do to scare us.
- I think I'm
gonna go check it out.
If y'all don't wanna come,
y'all can at least
wait for me down here.
- (laughs) I'll wait,
but if I hear anything,
I'm not coming guns blazing.
- I'll go with you.
- Mandy.
- What?
I wanna see,
and she shouldn't go alone.
- (laughs)
So I should wait here alone?
- Well, it's just up the
stairs. Just go to the landing.
(footsteps plodding)
(brooding music continues)
So what's up with you and
Parker? Do you know him?
- He hit me and
my dad drunk driving.
Yeah, my dad was in the
hospital for months,
and I had to drop outta
school and become a waitress.
- Fuck.
(floor creaking)
(blood squelching)
(ominous music)
- [Shelby] Behind you!
(door slamming)
- What the fuck was that?
What the hell what that?
- Just some creep in a mask.
- Well, well,
did you see who it was?
- No, I barely saw them
when they opened the door.
- Okay, well, uh, what about
the blood? Was that real?
- I mean, it's, it's all over
my shoe if you wanna taste it.
- [Tracy] Uh,
no, but I'll smell it.
- Okay.
(Tracy sniffing)
- Okay, well,
it's definitely blood,
but I don't know
if it's animal or not.
- How do you know
what blood smells like?
- I work in a restaurant.
I'm around bloody meat a lot.
(Shelby sniffs)
- Yeah, that is
what it smells like.
(hand smacking)
(Mandy and Shelby laughing)
- Okay, well, what do we do now?
- I think we should go back to
our rooms and wait this out.
- Yeah.
- Well, you can come wait
with us if you would like to.
- Mm.
- What?
- We're in
a contest for a million dollars
not working on a throuple.
- That's not what I meant,
but if something
is actually happening,
I feel like
we should stick together.
- Okay, it's fine.
We'll just, how about we listen
now for each other, okay?
We'll go to separate rooms.
I'm happy in my own, 'kay?
Let's go to our rooms.
(hands smacking)
(footsteps plodding)
- Let's go.
(brooding music)
(footsteps plodding)
(broom clattering)
(brooding music continues)
- (sighs) Fucking garbage.
(broom clattering)
(brooding music continues)
(drawer rasping)
(items clattering)
No fucking
knives? You kidding me?
(items clattering)
(sheath rasping and thudding)
(floor creaking)
(Tracy grunts)
(sighs) Okay,
that'll have to do.
(floor creaking)
(chair clattering)
(brooding music continues)
(Tracy exhaling)
(floor continues creaking)
It's gonna be
a long, long night.
(Tracy grunts)
(brooding music continues)
(camera whirring)
(footsteps plodding)
(brooding music)
(bottle rasping)
- Sweet.
(lid pops and thuds)
(glass clinking)
(bottle thuds)
(brooding music continues)
(glass thuds)
(Steven exhales)
- [Robert] What?
- [Parker] Looks like he
gonna be here for a while.
- Maybe there's another way in.
- No, oh, no, oh, no.
Hello.
What do we have here?
(lid clanking)
(brooding music continues)
(Steven sniffing)
(lips fluttering)
Jesus! What the...
(glass shattering)
(brooding music continues)
- Let's go.
- And what happened to you?
- I fell.
- The fuck,
is that fucking blood?
Jesus Christ!
Ah!
(dramatic music)
Holy shithead.
- The fuck are
you doing in my bar?
- What the fuck are
you doing with a bottle
of blood behind the bar
for me to fucking drink?
- You're not supposed to
fucking be here. (grunts)
(bodies thudding)
(both grunting)
(fists thudding)
(both continue grunting)
(Steven groans)
(Dusty screaming)
(gunshot blasting)
- [Robert] put it down
before I fucking
blow your head off.
(bat clattering)
(foot thudding)
(Dusty groaning)
(fists and feet thudding)
- Jesus, fucking...
Wait, wait, don't shoot.
(chair thuds)
(Dusty groaning)
(bodies thudding)
(brooding music)
(Steven breathing heavily)
- Not gonna start killing
people now, right?
- [Steven] How the hell
did you get a gun in here?
- I'm not who you think I am.
- [Steven] Yeah, no shit.
Who's Nathan, by the way?
- How do you know about Nathan?
- Well, I found your phone
in your, uh, hallway.
I guess you must
have dropped it, dumbass.
- I didn't drop
shit, motherfucker.
All right, someone must
have broken into my room.
- Whoa, whoa, stop,
stop. You had your phone?
So you've been in violation.
Are we out the game or not?
- I was never in the game.
- No, you're here for
the safe, and by the way,
your little buddy Nathan
promised to cut me in on
the deal
if I found your sorry ass.
- You didn't find shit.
(breathing heavily)
And I'm not
cutting you into anything.
- Oh, that's cool.
I guess I'll just tell Robert
about your little plan then,
and we'll all get disqualified.
- Who has the fucking gun here?
Now let's pick this fucker
up, tie him to a chair,
and I'm gonna go
get my fucking money.
- Okay, so where's the money?
- It's in the basement.
- I'll wait for you here. I'm
not going to the basement.
That killer or whatever is
down there is down there.
- That was the boiler room.
- Boiler room, basement,
it's all the same thing.
It goes up
under this whole hotel.
- Are you kidding me? Fuck.
- Well, let's go get that
money then, shall we?
- You know what, guys?
Um, I'ma just go home.
Y'all, y'all got it, all right?
- [Steven] Oh, just...
- I'll cut you in.
It's a story to
tell, lotta money.
- All right.
- [Steven] Cool, you guys
knock yourselves out.
I just got my ass kicked.
(footsteps plodding)
(brooding music continues)
(chair creaking)
- [Robert] All right,
here we go, here we go.
Here we go, here we go.
(items clattering)
(brooding music continues)
(rope creaking)
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
what do we have here?
Holy shit.
- You fucking pervert, you've
been watching the whole time.
- That creepy fucking weirdo.
- That's the motherfucker
who cut my throat.
- [Steven] Yo, yo, yo, wait up.
- Yo, miss lady.
(chair clattering)
Ma'am, ma'am.
(hand knocking)
Wake up.
There's someone
in your room, ma'am.
Wake up, yo, wake up, wake up.
- What?
- Okay, look.
I'm sorry to bother you but,
there's someone or
something in your place.
I saw it on Dusty's camera.
- What are
you trying to pull here?
(scoffs) Are
you drunk again or something?
- Okay, no, I'm not drunk,
and I, let me just say this
'cause I know nothing that I
do say is gonna matter to you.
I know that, and it shouldn't,
and I know you hate me
right now, and you should
'cause I would hate you,
but I am truly sorry
for the pain
I caused you and your dad
because of that accident.
- Accident?
- Yes.
- An accident is something
that can't be prevented.
My dad was in
the hospital for months.
He almost died.
- I'm sorry.
- Let alone both
of my legs got broken.
- And look, I know there's
something I could do
to make that right.
I know that, but I promise you,
when I win this competition,
I'll give you half of it,
or I'll help you get it.
I promise you that, 'kay?
- Well, there's
no time for that.
- No, no, we don't 'cause
someone is really in your place.
They've been in it. Let me
just, let me just show you.
(footsteps plodding)
(brooding music)
- [Robert] Wake
up, motherfucker.
(gun clattering)
- [Steven] Yo,
Robert, get up here.
- Okay, what is going on here?
- There was
a camera in this wall.
I think it was right here.
- Wait a second.
How do you know that?
- 'Cause Dusty's
been spying on you.
There's a lot of shit going on,
so we got him
tied up downstairs.
Now his phone fell out,
and there was a video
of you sleeping right now.
- Yeah, super creepy
guy standing over you.
I guess they yanked the
camera out of the wall.
- Same guy that,
that got after me.
- Okay, wait. Hold on a second.
How did
somebody even get in here?
I mean, I had the door
shut. I had it locked.
I even had a freaking
chair under the knob.
- Trap door maybe.
- Okay, I'm definitely not
staying in this room then,
And I don't trust any of you.
- [Robert] And
you're okay, so let's go.
- Yeah.
- Are you sure?
- Go.
- All right, I mean, okay.
(floor creaking)
(item clanking)
(brooding music continues)
(footsteps plodding)
- What the fuck?
Wait, wasn't he, what the fuck?
- Son of a bitch.
- That's that bullshit.
Fuck that. I'm out.
- Yo, dude, dude.
- You can have the money, man.
I'm out.
(doorknob clattering)
- Ah, you see?
- How am I gonna
find the fucking safe?
- Why don't
you call your buddy Nathan?
I'm sure he's got
some answers for ya.
(window creaking)
(brooding music continues)
- Oh, shit.
Motherfucker's out there.
- Oh, my God.
Uh, I think Charles is
dead up in his room, too.
Something is not right.
I mean, we heard a thud,
and there's blood coming
from under his door.
- See, I told
you you should go with us.
- I am not
leaving. I am winning this.
- People are really dying here.
Do you see this?
- I'm not.
I need this money. My
dad needs this money.
- Shit.
- [Steven] All right.
- So something's not adding up.
First, you have the young girl
that died, then the old man.
Now this guy's dead.
- What are you getting at?
- They're dead,
and we're still here.
- This isn't some fucking
horror movie, man.
- No, it isn't,
but something's not right.
(brooding music continues)
(blood squelching)
- Holy shit.
- Oh, oh.
They got
the blood texture right.
- Yeah, they did. Looks real.
Dude.
(footsteps plodding)
(brooding music continues)
- Whoa!
- What the fuck
did you do, man?
- Shitballs.
Oh, oh, could
you get me one, too?
Fuck me.
(liquid sloshing)
Whew, holy fucking shit.
(blood splashing)
(Steven exhales and laughs)
- If I'm gonna help out,
I'm gonna get fucked up.
(liquid sloshing)
(Parker exhales)
- [Robert]
I need to call Nathan.
- Dude, who is Nathan to you?
- He's my IT guy
at my brokerage firm.
- Uh, I thought
he was a US marshal.
- No, he's just a computer guy.
(Mandy screaming)
(brooding music continues)
- Babe, babe,
don't fall for this shit.
I don't trust any
of these shady guys.
By the way,
we found your chlorine bomb.
- Fuck you. I didn't do it.
- I was talking to Steven.
This shady fucker was
trying to kill us all
so he could get the prize money.
- I did not.
Besides, it's not nearly enough
chlorine to kill somebody.
- And even if there was,
it wouldn't have worked
'cause you put it in a
fucking plastic bottle.
I mean, it's a gas, not
an explosive, you idiot.
- I need to call Nathan.
- Phone's in my room, dipshit.
- No, it's not.
(hand thuds)
(brooding music continues)
(phone beeps)
(phone ringing)
- Who's this?
- Me.
- [Nathan] Oh,
fuck, where have you been?
- Been tied up.
- Did you find the others?
- [Robert] I did.
The whole gang's here.
- [Nathan] Are
we cutting 'em all in now?
- If I have to.
- You have to.
- Folks who ran the
hotel, they're all dead.
Can't find the safe, and
there's a killer here.
- [Nathan] Um, you mean, like,
one of you is the killer?
- It's impossible.
We were all upstairs
when they killed Dusty.
- I don't know about y'all,
but I'm tired of
looking at this shit.
Uh, and by the way, these
two, nowhere to be found,
and all of a sudden they show up
like they know what's
going on, so just saying.
- Shut up.
I went and grabbed them
up from their rooms.
Plus, there was
a point when all three
of us saw the masked
killer together, so...
- Unless that was Dusty.
(blanket rustling)
(brooding music continues)
- Nah, nah, 'cause when they
had me, I woke up like Dustin.
I mean, he could have
killed me, but he didn't.
That's why I thought it
was part of the game.
- I think we just need to see
if Charles is dead in his
room 'cause if he's not,
then he's obviously
responsible for all this.
- Yeah, I'm done
playing this game.
I'm going to find the
safe. Let's go, Parker.
- No, man, I told you I'm out.
I'm gonna get
these ladies to safety.
- Thank you, Parker.
- I'm with you, dude.
- Are you tracking us?
- Yes.
I'd go into the tool room
and into the crawl space.
(footsteps plodding)
(fist thudding)
- Charles, quit bullshitting.
Open this door, man.
(door clattering)
(Parker grunting)
- [Mandy] What? What is it?
- There's a body laying
down here. (grunts)
Well, that sure ain't Charles.
- Oh, my God.
- [Shelby]
Charles, are you in here?
Charles, where the fuck are you?
Charles, where are you-
- So is that a dummy?
- you fucking piece-
- Is it real?
- of shit?
Charles, I know you're in here,
you fucking asshole.
- He's dead,
for real dead.
- Where are you,
you son of a bitch?
- [Robert] Come on, Steven.
- [Steven] Dude,
wait the fuck up, man
I can't see anything.
And would
you slow the fuck down?
- [Robert] Sorry, this
is what we came here for.
(buckets clattering)
(brooding music continues)
- [Steven] Whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, man.
- No thank you.
- Holy shit.
I'm getting in there.
(item clattering)
(brooding music continues)
(Robert screaming)
(dramatic music)
Robert, what's
wrong? What's wrong?
- Maybe there's
a walkie-talk, or a gun,
phones, something.
Damn, nothing? Shit.
- Okay, we need to
obviously find a way
to contact the police.
I don't know.
- Why don't
you go get some help?
- I am not leaving here
until it's morning,
and I have a briefcase
full of cash in my hand.
- If you think
the game is still on,
you're as stupid as you look.
- What is wrong with you?
- Oh, there you go
again defending her.
- Defending her?
Uh, uh, you're just
being mean for no reason.
Where are you going?
- Stop.
- Wait, wait.
- Stay.
- Hey, she with us.
She shouldn't leave like that.
She shouldn't,
she shouldn't go alone.
- I'll go with her.
- All right.
- I just, I hate
when she gets like this.
She's just so insecure in it.
- I know, I know, and people
get crazy in times like this,
but let's go to the kitchen,
see if there's some knives
or something in there.
- Shelby, Shelby, wait.
(door clattering)
(Tracy sighs)
(brooding music)
(item thuds)
- Tracy!
(latch clicking)
What the fuck are you doing?
Tracy! Guys!
Get downstairs! Tracy!
Get the fuck away from her!
Get the fuck off of her!
Tracy! Guys!
Just get, get
the fuck away from her!
Tracy!
Hey, get the fuck off of her!
Guys, they're downstairs!
Tracy! Get
the fuck away from her!
Get the fuck off of her!
(knife rasping)
Tracy! Guys,
the killer's down here!
- [Parker] A knife or something.
You have no knife?
(brooding music continues)
Oh, shit.
- (screams) Oh, my God.
- [Parker] Uh.
- [Mandy] Fuck.
- Now is
that a dummy, or is he dead?
Is that real?
- Nope, he is dead.
- Well, check him
and see if he has, like,
a, a phone, weapon or something.
- Oh, my God, nope,
nothing, what do we do now?
- (sighs) I don't know.
- Where do you think Charles is?
- I don't know that either.
I mean, he can't, he's
too old to be trying
to run around here
speed of light trying
to scare us and shit, right?
- Yeah, and he's also way too
big for one person to carry.
I mean, he's
two-man job, for sure.
- Right, well,
let's just go down.
You check that room down there,
and I'll check over here.
(hands thudding)
- Tracy!
(Shelby exhales)
(glass shattering)
(brooding music continues)
(latch clicking)
Tracy, Tracy,
wake up, Tracy, babe.
We gotta get out here. Tracy.
Wake up. Come on, Tracy.
Tracy, Tracy.
Come on.
(door creaking)
- Ah!
(blood squelching)
(Robert coughing)
(door clattering)
Oh, fucking shit!
(Steven gasping)
(brooding music continues)
(glass shattering)
(Steven screaming)
(Steven gasping)
(brooding music continues)
- All right, let's see
if we can find some clues
or some weapons, information.
You check that room. I'm
gonna check this one.
Check those closets and
stuff for some clues.
(brooding music continues)
(mattress rustling)
(door squeaking)
Hey, yo, you good?
- [Mandy] Parker, look.
(item rustling)
(dramatic music)
(Mandy gasps)
(Mandy screaming)
- Yo, yo, open the door!
(door clattering)
Open the door!
Open this door! Open this door!
The fuck?
Mandy!
(door squeaking and clattering)
Shit.
- [Shelby] Come on. We
gotta get outta here.
Let's go. Come
on, come on, come on.
- Wait, wait.
Where are Mandy and Parker?
- [Shelby] I don't know.
We need to get outta here.
- We, we can't leave them.
- [Shelby] They're
gonna kill us. Come on.
- Wait. Just
get me up to my room.
I have a plan.
(Tracy screaming)
(glass shattering)
(feet pattering)
- Where you at?
(door clattering)
Mandy!
(feet pattering)
(bodies thudding)
Shit.
- Oh, my God,
that was almost so bad.
- You okay?
- We have to get Shelby.
- All right, and Mandy.
- Come on. Let's go
- Okay, let's do it.
(feet pattering)
- Shelby.
- Hold it right there.
- Charles, what are you doing?
- What are you doing here?
You left the building.
- So you're going around
killing people, huh?
- Ain't nobody dying.
It's all part of the game.
- Yeah, the game, it's
supposed to be the last one.
You killed
Dusty, your own daughter.
You tried to kill me, too.
- I wasn't trying to kill you.
Now hold it right there, missy.
- Come on. She needs help.
- What'd you do to her?
- What did I do? You did this.
This is all you.
- I've been in my fucking
room the whole time.
- Yeah, now there are
dead cop bodies upstairs.
- What are you talking about?
They're right were I staged 'em.
- No, no, no, no, those
aren't little dummies.
Throats are
slit. There's no pulse.
I checked. They're dead.
- Look, I don't know what
the fuck is going on here,
but we are all winning,
and you're gonna
owe us a lot of money.
- (laughs) Nah.
One guy had his cell
phone, violated the rules.
One guy left the building.
You went out the back door.
Looks like
you the two, only two left.
- We were already out,
right? Just let us leave.
- So we win?
- Not so fast, missy.
A couple hours left to sunup.
- Okay, okay, well,
look, congratulations.
I still wanna
help you and your dad,
but you can let me and her go.
I mean, we're already out,
right? Just let us leave.
- Not so fast, brother.
(brick thuds)
(Charles groans)
(knife rasping)
(body thudding)
(feet pattering)
(knife rasping)
(briefcase clattering)
(Tracy groans)
(body thudding)
(brooding music continues)
- Hey, you.
(glass shattering)
(dramatic music)
(killer coughing)
(dramatic music continues)
(mask thuds)
(killer continues coughing)
(door slamming)
(Tracy gasping)
(Tracy coughing)
(pensive music)
(pensive music continues)
Shelby, wake up.
(Shelby coughing)
(Parker gasping and coughing)
(Parker groaning)
(Parker gasping)
(pensive music continues)
(Tracy groaning)
(Shelby coughing)
(Tracy coughing)
(pensive music continues)
(sniffs) Oh, my God.
Mandy.
- You made it. We made it.
- Mandy didn't.
- Oh, shit.
- Shelby's alive.
(Parker breathing heavily)
- Go get help.
- Okay.
- Just go.
(Tracy coughing)
Oh, shit.
(pensive music continues)
(briefcase clattering)
(Shelby coughing)
(brooding music)
(Tracy coughing)
(siren wailing)
(brooding music continues)
- Ma'am, are you okay?
Are you a guest here?
- Yeah, I was.
There's still two people inside.
They need help.
- Do you know this young lady?
- Officer, that's her.
(knife rasping)
(knife thuds)
(blood squelching)
(knife rasping)
(head thuds)
(horn honking)
(Parker breathing heavily)
(water pattering)
(pensive music)
(Parker breathing heavily)
(drawers rasping)
(items clattering)
(book thuds)
(Parker breathing heavily)
- "Permanent injuries will
follow this young girl
for the entirety of her life.
(Parker breathing heavily)
Charges were dismissed when
she was unable to respond
to the interviewer's questions."
(Shelby groaning)
Sick motherfuckers.
Hey, hey, hey.
Wait, wait, wait.
(Shelby groaning)
Just relax. Hold on, hold on.
Relax.
Okay, look.
- Mandy? (groaning)
(sobbing) Mandy!
- [Parker] All right, look.
- Mandy!
- Tracy went for help.
I know, I know.
All right, look.
- Mandy!
- All right, look.
Now listen.
(Shelby sobbing)
The ambulance, come on.
Come on. Let's go slowly.
Come on.
(Parker grunting)
(Shelby sobbing)
Okay, come on, slowly.
I know, sh.
(Shelby sobbing)
(footsteps plodding)
(birds chirping)
(bodies thudding)
(tense music)
(brooding rock music)
(brooding rock music continues)
♪ Don't go in the house ♪
♪ At the end of the street ♪
♪ Or if you go inside,
you're just dead meat ♪
♪ I saw a silhouette
of a man with a mask ♪
♪ One look, he's gone
'cause he moves so fast ♪
♪ No, I won't go inside ♪
♪ Won't sleep tonight ♪
♪ Won't kill the lights ♪
♪ He's got a knife ♪
♪ I'm on the stairs ♪
♪ I feel so scared ♪
♪ It's just a dare ♪
♪ I won't go inside ♪
(brooding rock music continues)
♪ Don't go in the house ♪
♪ At the end of the street ♪
♪ Don't ask for tricks,
and don't ask for treats ♪
♪ The kids disappear ♪
♪ And don't leave a trace ♪
♪ There is a man inside,
but no one's seen his face ♪
♪ No, I won't go inside ♪
♪ Won't sleep tonight ♪
♪ Won't kill the lights ♪
♪ He's got a knife ♪
♪ I'm on the stairs,
I feel so scared ♪
♪ It's just a dare ♪
♪ I won't go inside ♪
♪ There's someone here ♪
♪ He's drawing near ♪
♪ I froze with fear ♪
♪ I nearly died ♪
♪ I'm all alone ♪
♪ And there's no phone ♪
♪ (indistinct) ♪
♪ Can't run, can't hide ♪
♪ Don't wanna die ♪
♪ He's got a knife ♪
♪ Don't go inside ♪
♪ I'm gonna die ♪
♪ He's got a knife ♪
♪ Can't run, can't hide ♪
♪ I'm gonna die ♪
(brooding rock music continues)
(solemn music)
(solemn music continues)
(engine humming)
(brooding music)
(door clattering)
- [Sheriff] No damn way.
(brooding music continues)